Guide to the Papers of Robert B. McKay 1919-1990 MC.208
New York University Archives
- Series I.
  - NJC Long-Range Plan, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - ABA TIPS TORT law and the public interest, 1920-1999 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Summary of Bar Council, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - ABA Long Range Planning Committee, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - NYU Law Schoool Debt Burden, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Papers on the Legal Profession, 1988-1990 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Prof Res. Conf., 1990 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - CPR Legal Program, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Manville Insurance, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - NYU Humanities Council, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Fall 1982 LO 9.3522 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - McGeorge School of Law, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Reimbursements RBM, 1980-1983 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - University of San Diego, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Tulsa University Speech, 1981-05-10 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Criminal Justice Panel, 1979-1983 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - University of Kansas, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - LCF Nominating Committee, 1982-1985 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Law School Admissions Council, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Loews Corporation, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Manville, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Torts Reform, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Tort Reform Commission, 1985-1987 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Manville, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Institute for Civil Justice, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Miscellanous, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Manville, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Goldstein vs. Goldstein, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - State Bar Discipline Monitor, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Task Force on Law Schools, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - TIPS, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - TIPS, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - TIPS, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Task Force on Law Schools, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Task Force on Law Schools, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Task Force on Law Schools, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - McKay Writings, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - McKay Writings, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - McKay Writings, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - McKay Writings, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - McKay Writings, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Assorted Journals with McKay Articles, 1965 (Box 33)
  - CPR Legal Program (ADR), 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - ADR Conference / Articles, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - ADR Conference / Articles, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Let's Talk Law - Scripts, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Dispute Resolution Center, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Criminal Justice / Legal Education, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - AALS / NALP Committee on Placement, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - AALS Notre Dame Inspection, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Puerto Rican Legal Defense Fund, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Miami Valley Paper Co., undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - ABA Graduate Legal Education Committee, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Judicial / Administration Seminar, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - ABA Special Committee on Products Liability, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - McKay Writings, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Journals / Newsletters, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Conferences, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Reports / Plans / Recommendations, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Articles / Journals, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Brigham Young University Law Review, 1977 (Box 34)
  - National Judicial College (NJC), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - ABCNY (Association of the Bar of the City of New York), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Annual Judicial Conference, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - National Judicial College, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - SALT (Society of American Law Teachers), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Supreme Court - Report of the Special Master (Georgia v. S. Carolina), 1988 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Volunteers of Legal Services, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - MALDEF (Mexican American Legal Defense and Educational Fund), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Revson Foundation, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1976-1979 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1976-1978 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - NY State Bar, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Legal Aid, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Philadelphia Police Study Task Force, undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Loews, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Fund for Modern Courts, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Manville Trust, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1976-1979 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Misc., 1990 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1975-1978 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1975-1978 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1977-1979 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Clippings and Article, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Citizens Union, 1988-1990 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Citizens Union, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Citizens Union, 1987-1990 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Citizens Union, 1986-1989 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Union, 1986-1989 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Tarabishi vs. McAlester Regional Hospital (binder), 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Legal Aid Society, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Legal Education/Professional Competence, 1980-1988 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Professional Independence of the Lawyer, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Legal Education/Professional Competence, 1980-1983 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Mandatory Continuing Legal Education, 1987-1990 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Mandatory Continuing Legal Education, 1987-1989 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Mandatory Continuing Legal Education, 1981-1988 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Goldstein vs. Goldstein, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Goldstein vs. Goldstein, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - University of Iowa Fall 1983 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Commission on Professionalism, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - ABA Lawyer Discipline, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - ABA TIPS Long Range Planning, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - ABA Young Lawyers Division, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - California Lawyer Discipline, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Property and Casualty Insurance: Fact or Fantasy?, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Written Testimony Vol II, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Product Liability, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - The Electoral Process in the U.S., 1988 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Outline Manual for Mass Tort Litigation, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Synar vs. United States of America, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Legal Aid Society Sentencing Guideline Cases, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - In Re Sealed Case ABA Amicus Curiae Brief, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Seperation of Powers Personal Notes, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - ABA Commission on Evaluation of Disciplinary Enforcement, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Commission on Evaluation of Disciplinary Enforcement - Written Testimony, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - ABA Commission on Evaluation of Disciplinary Enforcement, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - ABA Commission on Evaluation of Disciplinary Enforcement, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - ABA TIPS Professional Independence…Commission, 1987-1988 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - ABA, 1987-1990 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Cases and Materials on Affirmative Action, 1979-1983 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Misc. materials on professional responsibility and ethics, 1986-1990 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - American Law Institute Restatement of the Law, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - NYS Committee to Improve the Availability of Legal Services, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - NYSBA Committee on Professional Discipline Seminar, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - ABA TIPS Federal Product Liability, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - TORT Reform, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Civil Liberties Program - Yale, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Judicial Administration Class Syllabus, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - TIPS, 1984-1986 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - ABA/TIPS Task Force on Referenda, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Misc. ABA Correspondence, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Misc. ADR, 1987-1990 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Misc. ADR, 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Misc. ABA, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Misc. NYSBA, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Aspen Institute, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Philadelphia Police, 1983-1989 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Attica, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Lotteries, 1985-1990 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - A Student's Guide to Mediation and the Law, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Alternative Dispute Resolution Seminar, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Published Materials, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - NYU: Teaching, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Conflict Management Training Guide, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - State Ethics Commission - Meeting of June 2, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - State Ethics Commission, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Ethical Considerations in ADR by Robert McKay, undated (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - ABA Product Liability Hearings, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - ABA Product Liability Hearings, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - ABA Commission on Evaluation of Disciplinary Enforcement, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Published Materials, 1985-1989 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - ABA Correspondence, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - ABA Special Coordinating Committee on Professionalism, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - ABA Special Coordinating Committee on Professionalism, 1989-1990 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Constitutional Adjudication in a Presidential System of Government, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Virtue, Commerce and Lawyers, undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Materials on Lawyer Competence, 1987-1990 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - NYSBA Special Committee…Pro Bono Service, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - ABA Consortium on Professional Competence, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - ABA Conference on Professionalism, Ethics and Economic Change, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Misc. Materials on Reapportionment, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Bakke and Beyond Articles, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Bakke Related Issues, 1975-1978 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1978-1979 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Regents of UC v. Bakke, 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1977-1979 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Affirmative Action: Minority Enrollment, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action Clippings, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1975-1977 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Black Students in Higher Education - Judy Roizen, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Minority Education - Ford Foundation, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Law School Admissions Research, 1974-1976 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1973-1978 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1978-1979 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Affirmative Action: Bakke, 1974-1978 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Coordinating Council on Professional Competence, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Judicial Education on International Law (Judge Re), 1983 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Kutak Commission, 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - American Judicature Society, 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Citizens Union Research Foundation, 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Cromwell Dinner, 1977-1983 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Democracy Project, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - William O'Douglas Inquiry Paper, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Emory University, 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Fund for Modern Courts, 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Aspen Institute, 1986-1989 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Society of Fellows Seminar, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Seminar Readings on Justice and Society, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Sophocles I, undated (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Defenders Services Materials, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Aspen Institute, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Aspen Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Aspen Institute, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Aspen Institute Conference, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Articles and Other Writings, 1940s-1950s (Box 42, Folder 1-3)
  - Articles and Other Writings, 1960s (Box 42, Folder 4-5, Box 43, Folder 1-4)
  - Articles and Other Writings, 1970s (Box 43, Folder 5, Box 44, Folder 1-5, Box 45, Folder 1-4, Box 46, Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Articles and Other Writings, 1980s (Box 47, Folder 2-5, Box 50, Folder 1-4, Box 51, Folder 1-5, Box 52, Box 53, Box 54, Box 55, Box 56, Box 57, Box 58, Folder 1-2, Box 59)
  - Articles and Other Writings, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 3-4)